

IRYNA SKARAIEVA

Front-End Developer

I'm a Front-End Developer transitioning into IT after many years of working in education. My teaching experience has equipped me with strong analytical skills, problem-solving abilities, and teamwork capabilities. With a foundation in JavaScript, React and HTML/CSS, I focus on crafting functional, visually appealing web applications to enhance user experiences. Fast learner, adaptable, and detail-oriented.

CONTACT DETAILS

+421919495444

Trnava, Slovak Republic

LINKS TO OTHER RESOURCES

<u>Portfolio</u> <u>WhatsApp</u>

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

SCSS

React

Figma

Bulma

Tailwind CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teacher of Physics and Astronomy, Private Tutor

Self-Employed, Remote, UA, SK | Feb 2020 - Mar 2024 Medical College, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2014 - Aug 2015 Secondary School, Odesa, UA | Sep 2007 - Sep 2012

- \cdot Created educational materials, building skills in multimedia.
- · Developed instructional documentation.
- · Managed the educational process for a home-schooled student.
- · Supervised student groups.

Content Manager

Freelance, Vinnytsya, UA | Feb 2016 - May 2017

- \cdot Editing and managing website content using the Content Management System.
- ·Strict compliance with requirements and deadlines.

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Native

Russian C2

English B1

Slovak B1

DRIVING LICENSE

В

EDUCATION

The Faculty of Physics and Mathematics

Teacher of Physics, Computer Science and Life Safety Basics **Master's degree** Sep 2002 — June 2007

South Ukrainian National Pedagogical University named after K. D. Ushynsky